<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0" xmlns:cc="http://cyber.law.harvard.edu/rss/creativeCommonsRssModule.html">
    <channel>
<title>
<![CDATA[ Stories by Polylastic on Medium ]]>
</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[ Stories by Polylastic on Medium ]]>
</description>
<link>https://medium.com/@polylastic?source=rss-5cf14b881f98------2</link>
<image>
<url>https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/fit/c/150/150/1*_YdiO9XT-wRrl8DBXNQ0Ag.jpeg</url>
<title>Stories by Polylastic on Medium</title>
<link>https://medium.com/@polylastic?source=rss-5cf14b881f98------2</link>
</image>
<generator>Medium</generator>
<lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 02:45:02 GMT</lastBuildDate>
<atom:link href="https://medium.com/@polylastic/feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
<webMaster>
<![CDATA[ yourfriends@medium.com ]]>
</webMaster>
<atom:link href="http://medium.superfeedr.com" rel="hub"/>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[ Polylastic: New and Noteworthy ]]>
</title>
<link>https://polylastic.medium.com/polylastic-new-and-noteworthy-a409f403a322?source=rss-5cf14b881f98------2</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://medium.com/p/a409f403a322</guid>
<category>
<![CDATA[ nft ]]>
</category>
<category>
<![CDATA[ defi ]]>
</category>
<category>
<![CDATA[ cryptocurrency ]]>
</category>
<category>
<![CDATA[ bitcoin ]]>
</category>
<category>
<![CDATA[ ethereum ]]>
</category>
<dc:creator>
<![CDATA[ Polylastic ]]>
</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Mon, 06 Sep 2021 21:17:17 GMT</pubDate>
<atom:updated>2021-09-06T21:17:17.822Z</atom:updated>
<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[ <figure><img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*4qqRHbYr-8KrwYKYjSyUqA.jpeg" /></figure><p>It has been a whirlwind start for Polylastic; from our storied beginnings and directly into a bear market cycle and beyond. It has been fraught with challenges whilst behind the scenes, there has been a great deal of development, iterating and steady progress.</p><p>Over time, the vision has been revealed in pieces, some would say fragments and this was somewhat by design as well as necessity. We are more bullish than ever on the future of systematic investment plans in the realm of blockchain. The inflow of crypto investors, both institutional and retail along with the steady adoption of crypto on the whole, speaks to a growing need for “plug and play” style contribution. We have not faltered in this regard and our end game has always been to create a token utility that rewards the assets and communities of the tokens we aspire to support.</p><p>At no fault of our great community, we had to remain tight-lipped about some forthcoming changes which we believe to be bullish. The project has continued to evolve and iterate, engendering changing needs and additional resource requirements. Polylastic will forever be a work in progress and continue to evolve but at this juncture, we’d like to share some upcoming news and deliver some overdue information.</p><p><strong>The upgrade on Kucoin</strong> — we have requested they upgrade directly to Version 3 as the V2 upgrade is still pending. We are working with Kucoin to make the upcoming upgrade to Version 3 as seamless as practically possible and are confident that we will gain community support on the upgrade.</p><p><strong>Timelines</strong> — this has also been a source of frustration for us and our lack of communication is certainly not a lack of consideration to you. There were simply too many moving parts at any given time and we determined that in the short term, no news was preferable to potentially inaccurate news. Management realizes the mistake herein and will take corrective steps to ensure that a better flow of communication is provided.</p><p><strong>Overall</strong>: We are continuing to work with a top-notch agency along with inhouse development and a number of independent contractors, however, we are adding additional resources as we near launch. The aim is both to fast track development into launch as well as to have necessary eyes on the post-launch working product. The overarching theme here is that the continued evolution of Polylastic should be relatively seamless and expeditious.</p><p><strong>Product</strong>: The product development itself has been steady and although we’ve made upgrades and changes, it has remained on course. It is not a contract that once deployed will remain static. We plan to add features and functionality to optimize the market offerings as well as the POLX token. This is, for the long-term, our most important consideration and will remain firmly affixed in the crosshairs of our focus. Our initial consideration was to put more resources on the project and so we did. The result, while not problematic or redundant, slowed things some as each new party needed to be apprised and brought up to date in order to move forward. The net result is something we are quite pleased with.</p><p><strong>Rewards</strong>: As we come close to revealing some really exciting developments, we wanted to reward our loyal holders in the interim. We have decided to extend staking for an additional month while creating our product. This building of the ecosystem requires a sustainable level of volume for the taxation in order to provide a level of yield that can be deemed adequate.</p><p><strong>Personnel</strong>: At this point, we are nearing beta launch and the additional people power we’ve deployed are now in stride and sync. We were very selective in narrowing down the talent for the new Polylastic and are proud to announce the following additions to the Polylastic team.</p><p><strong>Meet Our Newest Members:</strong></p><figure><img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1002/0*UhdslbV791frfLYU" /></figure><p>Director</p><p>Brandon Xavier is a business entrepreneur and inventor, with a background in finance. He has a passion for blockchain technology and predicting market trends, having applied his experience and knowledge to several projects in recent years. He is very excited about strategizing with the team and using his skills to help see Polylastic to its full potential within the growing sector of systematic investing.</p><figure><img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/984/0*hJFIgQLjUsP09K6M" /></figure><p>Director</p><p>KD Likakis is a highly experienced marketing and finance expert, with a love for all things blockchain. He has been involved in many successful projects within the realm of cryptocurrency and brings vast experience with him to the Polylastic team. He is looking forward to implementing his skillset to help fuel the growth of this project.</p><figure><img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/856/0*Dh8EI0Olund7Eag0" /></figure><p>Director</p><p>Niko Sairanen has an extensive background in software development, graphic design, and marketing. He has been involved in the cryptocurrency space for over 8 years and has worked on multiple successful blockchain projects. He has coded for some very successful companies across multiple blockchains. He is excited to bring his subject matter experience to the Polylastic team.</p><p>Finally, we would like to offer our community an apology. Due to a multitude of reasons, we were unable to reveal more information about what was taking place behind the scenes. At this juncture, we would like to thank Sunil for his unwavering support and contribution towards Polylastic thus far, as he takes on a new role as an advisor to the project. Sunil was a true catalyst for Polylastic and remains the embodiment of an ecosystem champion. His passion and fervor for the project has been unwavering and will continue in this stead. While some may resort to conjecture regarding the specifics, we’d like to emphasize that this is something that was collectively decided in respect to the natural progression of things. The reality is that we all serve the project above ourselves and must collectively determine the best course for it. Unfortunately in crypto, everything is under scrutiny, for right and wrong and we assure you that everyone involved thus far has only had the best interest of the project. We would once again like to thank Sunil for his patience, and contributions towards Polylastic, and are looking forward to everything that’s to come.</p><h3>Join Polylastic</h3><p><a href="http://polylastic.io/"><strong>Website</strong></a><strong> | </strong><a href="https://twitter.com/polylastic"><strong>Twitter</strong></a><strong> | </strong><a href="https://t.me/polylastic"><strong>Telegram</strong></a></p><img src="https://medium.com/_/stat?event=post.clientViewed&referrerSource=full_rss&postId=a409f403a322" width="1" height="1" alt=""> ]]>
</content:encoded>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[ Don’t Call It A Comeback ]]>
</title>
<link>https://polylastic.medium.com/dont-call-it-a-comeback-5dbd83eb3348?source=rss-5cf14b881f98------2</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://medium.com/p/5dbd83eb3348</guid>
<category>
<![CDATA[ polylastic-upgrade ]]>
</category>
<category>
<![CDATA[ index-funds ]]>
</category>
<category>
<![CDATA[ polx ]]>
</category>
<category>
<![CDATA[ polx-v3 ]]>
</category>
<dc:creator>
<![CDATA[ Polylastic ]]>
</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2021 00:15:23 GMT</pubDate>
<atom:updated>2021-07-26T00:15:23.798Z</atom:updated>
<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[ <figure><img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*Qw1Uig03zGTgGGpn-PaO8g.jpeg" /></figure><p>Despite market sentiment and circumstances beyond our current control, Polylastic continues to iterate. We remain steadfast in our belief and understanding pertaining to the importance of indicized products in crypto. Its historical merit can not be impugned and we must take the very best of the traditional—soon to be legacy systems—and go further.</p><p>One of the pillars of our future success lies in an aggressive taxation structure. As the POLX token goes through re-distribution to ultimately end up with those who see beyond near-term speculation, it is an imperative that we support these holders.</p><h4>Forthcoming Structure</h4><p>Again, there are still moving parts that we can not rely on but felt it was incumbent upon us to share our plans as the time nears.</p><p>The primary tenets:</p><ul><li>A 9% Network Tax will be imposed; to be utilized as follows—</li><li>33.3% of the POLX tax (3% of the total transacted) will be earmarked to provide deeper liquidity on Pancake Swap.</li><li>33.3% of the POLX tax (3% of the total transacted) will be distributed to holders.</li><li>22.2% (2% of the total transacted ) will be burnt.</li><li>11.1% (1% of the total transacted) will be distributed as community rewards to users who help promote POLX.</li></ul><h4>Implications</h4><p>The reasons for this are myriad. Certainly, there is a level of gamification that traditional finance players simply can not impose despite the significant benefits. Secondarily, this structure creates a hyper-deflationary mechanism that we believe, will truly reveal its potency over time. Additionally, the distribution to supporters funnels the tokens into the most deserving wallets.</p><p>Consider:</p><ul><li>This represents upto 500% increase from the original burn targets.</li><li>Trading volume, irrespective of buying or selling, translates to deeper liquidity</li><li>Perpetual Rewards: Hodling gains additional POLX from every network transaction.</li><li>Ongoing Community Rewards: The top community members who promote POLX on social media are rewarded periodically. This can help to nurture a community powered growth engine.</li></ul><p>This cyclical approach creates a self-sustaining network that provides ongoing incentives to the real users whilst deflation aggressively continues.</p><h4>Final Thoughts</h4><p>This is a marathon not a sprint. Though it would have been ideal to see everything fall into place immediately, we have all endured through various hiccups; some of which are ongoing. Though we can say with a measure of certitude that it is not all our doing, we do take 100% responsibility and will continue to develop as the past does not equal the future. In the biggest picture of all, we believe Polylastic is poised to be a form of futuristic style of investing with a double deflationary burn structure and we have learned from those who came before us. Structurally, there have been a number of well-intended projects that have attempted similar with sub-optimal results due to their lack of real utility. We have taken note, refined our objectives and approach in order to create a utility token and tokenomics that make the product compelling, interactive and user-incentivized.</p><img src="https://medium.com/_/stat?event=post.clientViewed&referrerSource=full_rss&postId=5dbd83eb3348" width="1" height="1" alt=""> ]]>
</content:encoded>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[ Polylastic gets Bonded! ]]>
</title>
<link>https://polylastic.medium.com/polylastic-gets-bonded-43b10d0cb300?source=rss-5cf14b881f98------2</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://medium.com/p/43b10d0cb300</guid>
<category>
<![CDATA[ polx ]]>
</category>
<category>
<![CDATA[ yield-farming ]]>
</category>
<category>
<![CDATA[ bonded-finance ]]>
</category>
<category>
<![CDATA[ usb ]]>
</category>
<category>
<![CDATA[ polylasyic ]]>
</category>
<dc:creator>
<![CDATA[ Polylastic ]]>
</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 11:02:21 GMT</pubDate>
<atom:updated>2021-06-15T11:02:21.970Z</atom:updated>
<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[ <p>As a builder of contemporary versions of the time-honored index trackers, Polylastic forthcoming products ooze with innovation. From direct staking to deflationary features along with a continuously iterating basket of assets, our aim to reinvent a traditional finance staple is well underway.</p><p>The promise of crypto is both being realized and continues to tantalize with possibilities. As Polylastic matures and releases, it will be clear that what we are building is not your father’s mutual fund but something far more dynamic. Historically, indexes are the safest, most profitable approach for investors. The dollar cost averaging into a group of promising assets is bear market proof but in tradfi, a static undertaking. Polylastic is doing so much more to ensure its growth by contributing to its own success. By now, users are familiar with Polylastic as aggregator with a focus on DeFi products. It brings marketing capabilities and captive communities to everything it does and now, thanks to Bonded Finance, is able to offer something more.</p><figure><img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*Qw5kbAHcfzgBiMij8k6oTw.jpeg" /></figure><h4>The Bonded Solution</h4><p>One of Bonded’s smart instruments bundles altcoins into a basket, mints synthetic Ethereum or USB (the Bond stable coin) against these assets, and allows that money earn yields when locked in a given DeFi contract. Bonded’s smart instruments offer index style products in their own right. One of the primary differences is that Polylastic holds assets under management so to speak. As POLX is staked, new assets are voted in versus users opting in and out.</p><p>In our initial exploration with Bonded, the concept of an integrative cross chain solution could allow for Polylastic assets to earn yield while they are being held, could bring yet another wrinkle into the future of DeFi. We’ve come together to explore how the assets of Polylastic and the POLX token can be utilized in our smart contracts so the tokens can have their own earning power. We are entirely complementary projects with a vision to make DeFi accessible, user friendly, layered and potent.</p><p>While traditional index funds are not new to crypto, the end-to-end pedigreed, active solution is missing. Polylastic as an aggregator, marketer and the ecosystem builder must be forward looking and utilizing the communal aspects of crypto to gain user-ship and promote DeFi is a step ahead. Securing yield for the projects we not only tout but hold is a coup. The builders and supporters of DeFi are our audience as we redefine money and set it on a globally inclusive course.</p><p>Bonded is here to help altcoins flourish by giving them the opportunity to earn. They are out to make the promising, less established become the established. Polylastic is much the same in spirit and we are proud to be partnering with Bond.</p><h4>About Bonded.Finance</h4><p>The Bonded platform was created to incubate and deploy experimental, high-yield, smart-contract driven financial instruments that push the bounds of open finance. Bonded is an algorithmic model that aims to unlock, aggregate, and de-risk ~50 billion in dormant value distributed amongst untapped digital assets by allowing supporters of qualifying altcoin projects the opportunity to leverage assets and realize their value.</p><p><a href="http://bonded.finance/">Website </a>| <a href="https://twitter.com/bondedfinance">Twitter</a> |<a href="https://t.me/bondedfinance"> Telegram</a></p><h3>-Polylastic</h3><p><a href="http://polylastic.io/"><strong>Website</strong></a><strong> | </strong><a href="https://twitter.com/polylastic"><strong>Twitter</strong></a><strong> | </strong><a href="https://t.me/polylastic"><strong>Telegram</strong></a></p><img src="https://medium.com/_/stat?event=post.clientViewed&referrerSource=full_rss&postId=43b10d0cb300" width="1" height="1" alt=""> ]]>
</content:encoded>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[ Introducing Peak Weeks ]]>
</title>
<link>https://polylastic.medium.com/introducing-peak-weeks-72f3adbd25de?source=rss-5cf14b881f98------2</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://medium.com/p/72f3adbd25de</guid>
<category>
<![CDATA[ yield-farm ]]>
</category>
<category>
<![CDATA[ polylastic-farm ]]>
</category>
<category>
<![CDATA[ polylastic ]]>
</category>
<category>
<![CDATA[ defi ]]>
</category>
<category>
<![CDATA[ peak-week ]]>
</category>
<dc:creator>
<![CDATA[ Polylastic ]]>
</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2021 20:20:13 GMT</pubDate>
<atom:updated>2021-06-17T00:53:51.289Z</atom:updated>
<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[ <figure><img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*wgquuX0LfHV_8c7_NleTuQ.jpeg" /></figure><p>Polylastic Farms, our inaugural yield farming program has been a grand success. With active participants in the campaign likely to earn perpetual passive income, we believe that crypto farming will be heralded as a boon for early adopters.</p><h4>Taxation Integration Update</h4><p>In assessing of our path to date, we have had to navigate through several obstacles and the delay in the re-opening of deposits and withdrawals for POLX V2 tokens on Kucoin has been chief among them. Driving innovation is not easy and we see these growing pains as touchstones for growth. Kucoin has been a key differentiator for Polylastic and an ally, but integrating the Network Taxation features in a timely fashion on Kucoin has been challenging. We’d like to apologize for the inconvenience but would also like to thank Kucoin for supporting such a complex tax structure and for being so hands on in our efforts to get it right in a secure way. We expect these issues to be resolved next week.</p><h4><strong>Life On the Farm</strong></h4><p>There are major changes coming to Polylastic Farms. Whilst POLX staking will remain open at all times, the yield farming pools will only be open at selected time intervals. With the <strong>Peak Week</strong> going live from today, the following changes will be instituted:</p><ol><li>Yield Farming Pools will remain open for 1 week every month, starting today, 11th June, 2021.</li><li><strong>“Peak Week”</strong>—Liquidity providers will be able to supply liquidity for the POLX/BNB pool on PancakeSwap during this week only. They can then stake the L.P token to access high APYs on <a href="https://farm.polylastic.io">farm.polylastic.io</a>.</li><li>During the Peak Week, buys or sells on <a href="https://exchange.pancakeswap.finance/#/swap">Pancakeswap</a> will not incur any network taxes.</li><li>At the end of Peak Week, all buys and sells on <a href="https://exchange.pancakeswap.finance/#/swap">Pancakeswap</a> will incur taxes and users will not be allowed to supply liquidity on <a href="https://exchange.pancakeswap.finance/#/swap">Pancakeswap </a>for the POLX/BNB pair.</li><li>Peak Week will be one week out of every month.</li></ol><h4><strong>The First Peak Week:</strong></h4><p><strong>Start Date: </strong>11th June 2021.</p><p><strong>End Date: </strong>17th June 2021, 12:00:00 PM UTC.</p><p>For those still new to farming and the Polylastic offering, please refer to this <a href="https://polylastic.medium.com/ready-set-farm-2d3f0715d53e">article</a> to get started. Hope to see you out there!</p><h3>-Polylastic</h3><p><a href="http://polylastic.io/"><strong>Website</strong></a><strong> | </strong><a href="https://twitter.com/polylastic"><strong>Twitter</strong></a><strong> | </strong><a href="https://t.me/polylastic"><strong>Telegram</strong></a></p><img src="https://medium.com/_/stat?event=post.clientViewed&referrerSource=full_rss&postId=72f3adbd25de" width="1" height="1" alt=""> ]]>
</content:encoded>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[ In Pursuit of Fairness ]]>
</title>
<link>https://polylastic.medium.com/in-pursuit-of-fairness-286d2bb5805d?source=rss-5cf14b881f98------2</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://medium.com/p/286d2bb5805d</guid>
<category>
<![CDATA[ polylastic-tax ]]>
</category>
<category>
<![CDATA[ polylastic ]]>
</category>
<category>
<![CDATA[ network-tax ]]>
</category>
<dc:creator>
<![CDATA[ Polylastic ]]>
</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 19:44:40 GMT</pubDate>
<atom:updated>2021-06-04T19:44:40.851Z</atom:updated>
<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[ <p>Currently, for technical reasons unrelated to us, deposits and withdrawals on Kucoin will not be available for a few days. Although it is a common occurrence and an ultimately mundane one, Polylastic believes that this could imbalance our burgeoning market place. As a newer project, it is important to us to remain on kilter and this is an opportunity for us to step up to provide protection and value for our supporters. The network taxation is an integral feature to our network and getting it started in balanced conditions is an imperative.</p><p>To spell things out:</p><ul><li>Deposits and withdrawals are temporarily unavailable on Kucoin.</li><li>All tokens on Kucoin arrived prior to network taxation.</li><li>Centralized exchange trades can not be taxed directly, however, deposits and withdrawals into exchanges will incur a tax.</li><li>Tax on deposits and withdrawals levels the playing field across markets.</li></ul><p>Currently:</p><ul><li>Deposits and withdrawals on Kucoin are temporarily unavailable.</li><li>Kucoin is siloed right now.</li></ul><p>Until it resumes, unfair market conditions could prevail whereby:</p><ul><li>Pancakeswap trades may get taxed.</li><li>Trades on Kucoin may not be, even indirectly.</li></ul><p>Therefore:</p><ul><li>Network taxation for trades on Pancakeswap are suspended until deposits/withdrawals on Kucoin resume.</li><li>Network taxes will continue to be incurred by all transfers.</li></ul><p>Our long-term goal is the implementation of an aggressive tax structure that will ultimately provide scarcity and value realization for the POLX token. It is not a near-term effort and it is advantageous to the network to provide users additional time for the market place to balance. The taxation structure is aimed to benefit our supporters who see the long-term potential in passive, enduring income.</p><p>The POLX token lies at the heart of all we do and these measures are encoded to be firm and fair. In the very short term, to ensure an equitable marketplace we will offer additional time for users to build positions, stake, farm, trade and navigate without discrimination. In due course, we will have additional channels of distribution for the POLX token but as of now, it is our opportunity to inject a measure of fairness into the market. We do not wish to play favorites or gamify, in any way, our organic growth.</p><h3>-Polylastic</h3><p><a href="http://polylastic.io/"><strong>Website</strong></a><strong> | </strong><a href="https://twitter.com/polylastic"><strong>Twitter</strong></a><strong> | </strong><a href="https://t.me/polylastic"><strong>Telegram</strong></a></p><img src="https://medium.com/_/stat?event=post.clientViewed&referrerSource=full_rss&postId=286d2bb5805d" width="1" height="1" alt=""> ]]>
</content:encoded>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[ Ready, Set…FARM! ]]>
</title>
<link>https://polylastic.medium.com/ready-set-farm-2d3f0715d53e?source=rss-5cf14b881f98------2</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://medium.com/p/2d3f0715d53e</guid>
<category>
<![CDATA[ polylastic-yield-farming ]]>
</category>
<category>
<![CDATA[ polx ]]>
</category>
<category>
<![CDATA[ polx-farming ]]>
</category>
<category>
<![CDATA[ polylastic ]]>
</category>
<category>
<![CDATA[ polx-staking ]]>
</category>
<dc:creator>
<![CDATA[ Polylastic ]]>
</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 16:13:12 GMT</pubDate>
<atom:updated>2021-06-04T16:13:12.954Z</atom:updated>
<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[ <figure><img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*99ccGzjd3kWujcNFXud5zQ.jpeg" /></figure><p>Now, following the token upgrade, taxation and continued evolution of Polylastic, it’s time for our growing army to enjoy some peace and spend some time on the farm to earn rewards.</p>< ]]>
<![CDATA[ p>With healthy ecosystem rewards coming into the fold along with with the removal of approximately 360m tokens from circulation, the POLX community is set to earn some rewards. We feel the introduction of our inaugural farming program is a great way to come out of the tunnel of a recent development pipeline that was pressing.</p><p>The initial farming and subsequent reward are in lockstep with our vision to produce an autonomous and dynamic suite of indices catered to an ever-moving market and a captive audience. In due course, these products will reflect our users and these denizens, these contributors must be rewarded. This initializing is to put a cornerstone into the foundation of a larger vision. As these contracts get underway, it signifies the beginning of a movement in DeFi—to offer not just comparable instruments seen in traditional finance but appreciable improvements over them. The builders, the champions, the aggregators, accelerators and community must be rewarded commensurately with our growth. Polylastic is a dynamic and fluid solution to an antiquated financial services industry that always excluded smaller participants. Farming is a critical first step in achieving these goals.</p><p>Polyastic’s Farm and the targeted distribution of POLX represent the first migratory activities on our platform as a fully distributed system set to challenge the dated paradigm of legacy finance. Polylastic will remain nimble in order to create a sustainable, more resilient and bear market proof framework. The POLX token is the driver that powers the circuitry and this embryonic stage distribution is, for us, a watershed moment.</p><h3>The Polylastic Farm</h3><p>Our farming and rewards is live and participants can provide liquidity tokens via the POLX-BNB pair or offer single-sided staking on our own portal. The URL is: <strong>farm.polylastic.io</strong></p><p>Naturally, liquidity providers will receive a higher rate given the risk of IL or impermanent loss. Moreover, strengthening the books with liquidity is an active demonstration of support that requires twice the capital provisions (in terms of both BNB and POLX). Those who wish to be more hands-off are certainly more than welcome to begin with one-sided staking on our own portal.</p><h4>POLX Farming Rewards:</h4><ul><li><strong>Commencement:</strong> 6/04/2021.</li><li><strong>Completion</strong>: Perpetual. Rewards will be added continually to incentivise longer term farming.</li><li><strong>Reward Pool: 1 Billion POLX</strong> tokens will be set aside initially for rewarding our farmers and POLX stakers. This number is likely to grow with time.</li><li><strong>Daily Distribution</strong>: approximately, <strong>2.74 million POLX</strong> will be distributed as rewards daily.</li></ul><h4>Divvying Up the POLX Rewards:</h4><ul><li><strong>POLX-(Single-Side)</strong>: 40%.</li><li><strong>POLX-BNB LP</strong>: 60%.</li></ul><h4>The All Important Schedule</h4><p>The token emission schedule for Polylastic is dynamic in nature. Individuals often debate the level of attractiveness of high vs. lower APYs and typically state:</p><ul><li>Higher APY is flashy, more tokens, but less valuable and dilutive while</li><li>Lower APY is sustainable, demonstrates token value and prudence, etc.</li></ul><p>This is merely the beginning of these debates and something Polylastic has a clear stance on. Our emission schedule, like Polylastic itself is mobile, dynamic, nimble and most of all—flexible. We have earmarked a minimum of <strong>1 Billion POLX tokens </strong>and will carefully monitor in order to ensure a healthy APY while distributing tokens into the market strategically.</p><p>Emissions should be a function of demand, usage, utility and a vehicle to facilitate desired distribution. We will have metrics and data being delivered by our users in the form of staking which are the chief determinants. We are here to reward early adopters but not flood the market to deter future interest. Be it fixed or variable, rates fluctuate based on the number of tokens being staked and this is what we will monitor. Any changes will be announced.</p><p><strong>How to upgrade: </strong>Please read<strong> </strong><a href="https://polylastic.medium.com/the-polylastic-token-upgrade-c6dd3f2b725c">https://polylastic.medium.com/the-polylastic-token-upgrade-c6dd3f2b725c</a> for detailed info. Only upgraded V2 POLX tokens can be staked or farmed.</p><p><strong>How to stake POLX:</strong></p><ul><li>Visit: <a href="https://farm.polylastic.io/"><strong>https://farm.polylastic.io/</strong></a></li><li>Connect your BSC enabled metamask wallet that holds your upgraded V2 POLX tokens.</li><li>Enter the desired amount of POLX you wish to stake.</li><li>Click Approve POLX and continue to confirm the transaction on Metamask.</li><li>Confirm the desired amount of POLX tokens that you wish to stake and confirm the transaction using Metamask.</li></ul><p><strong>How to stake LP tokens:</strong></p><ul><li>Provide liquidity for the BNB&lt;&gt; Polylastic v2 pair on Pancakeswap. (<a href="https://exchange.pancakeswap.finance/#/add/ETH/0xbe510da084E084e3C27b20D79C135Dc841135c7F">https://exchange.pancakeswap.finance/#/add/ETH/0xbe510da084E084e3C27b20D79C135Dc841135c7F</a>).</li><li>Navigate to the LP staking page on <a href="https://farm.polylastic.io/"><strong>https://farm.polylastic.io/</strong></a><strong>.</strong></li><li>Enter the desired amount of LP tokens and approve POLX-BNB via metamask.</li><li>Confirm the desired amount of LP tokens to be staked and confirm the transaction using Metamask.</li></ul><p>We’d like to thank everyone for supporting the Polylastic vision as it unfurls. We have come a long way in a short time together and very much value those of you who came early and are beginning to realize the potency of passive income as a time-honored way to accrue wealth. Polylastic aims to bring the index into the 21st Century and deliver it to the masses, as packaged and innovated on by us and our contributors. We look forward to sharing more in the coming days!</p><h3>-Polylastic</h3><p><a href="http://polylastic.io/"><strong>Website</strong></a><strong> | </strong><a href="https://twitter.com/polylastic"><strong>Twitter</strong></a><strong> | </strong><a href="https://t.me/polylastic"><strong>Telegram</strong></a></p><img src="https://medium.com/_/stat?event=post.clientViewed&referrerSource=full_rss&postId=2d3f0715d53e" width="1" height="1" alt=""> ]]>
</content:encoded>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[ The Polylastic Token Upgrade ]]>
</title>
<link>https://polylastic.medium.com/the-polylastic-token-upgrade-c6dd3f2b725c?source=rss-5cf14b881f98------2</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://medium.com/p/c6dd3f2b725c</guid>
<category>
<![CDATA[ polylastic-token-swap ]]>
</category>
<category>
<![CDATA[ polylastic ]]>
</category>
<category>
<![CDATA[ polylastic-token-upgrade ]]>
</category>
<dc:creator>
<![CDATA[ Polylastic ]]>
</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 01:32:30 GMT</pubDate>
<atom:updated>2021-06-04T14:19:35.759Z</atom:updated>
<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[ <figure><img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*ZCN-gmxHrYY_YbbUvmho6A.jpeg" /></figure><p>The anticipated Network Taxation for Polylastic transactions is set to go live at approximately 2:00pm UTC on 4th June, 2021.</p><p>The original contract <strong>0xe29ac6ea53dea5211155f9d7c8c41beee852efa0</strong> will be deprecated as the implementation of the network taxation structure is encoded in the new smart contract. POLX token holders will need to upgrade existing POLX tokens to the new version with the following contract address:</p><p><strong>0xbe510da084E084e3C27b20D79C135Dc841135c7F</strong></p><h4><strong>To perform the token upgrade:</strong></h4><p>Tokens held on Kucoin or staked on Pool-x, the tokens will be automatically upgraded and our users need not take any additional steps.</p><p>For those who hold tokens outside of Kucoin on a BSC compatible wallet, please follow the below mentioned steps:</p><ul><li>Sign in to Metamask on a compatible browser (Chrome or Brave). If you are unfamiliar with the usage of Metamask, please read <a href="https://academy.binance.com/en/articles/how-to-use-metamask">https://academy.binance.com/en/articles/how-to-use-metamask</a> to learn how to setup and initialise Metamask.</li><li>Connect to the Binance Smart Chain network on Metamask. To learn more, please read <a href="https://academy.binance.com/en/articles/connecting-metamask-to-binance-smart-chain">https://academy.binance.com/en/articles/connecting-metamask-to-binance-smart-chain</a>.</li><li>Users may also be able to use Trust Wallet browser application on Chrome / supported browsers. The mobile app is not compatible with our token upgrade, airdrop and yield farming portals. We would recommend that they use Metamask instead.</li><li>If you hold your POLX on trust wallet, export the recovery phrase/private key and add the account on Metamask.</li><li>Make sure that you hold BNB in your desired wallet to facilitate transactions on the BSC network.</li><li>Login to the web portal: <a href="https://portal.polylastic.io/"><strong>https://portal.polylastic.io/</strong></a></li><li>Click on “Connect Wallet” at the top right corner of the web portal and connect the desired account to the web portal.</li><li>The portal will automatically show the amount of POLX tokens held in the wallet. Click on “Upgrade” and continue the process on Metamask.</li><li>You will need to approve the token on Metamask and then confirm the transaction.</li><li>Once the transaction is confirmed, your wallet will automatically reflect the new version of the token.</li></ul><p>That’s it. If you reach this stage, then Congratulations! you have successfully upgraded the token.</p><h4><strong>Pre-IDO Airdrop Rewards</strong></h4><p>Following the token upgrade, the portal to claim the airdrop will be live on June 4th—at approximately 2:15pm UTC.</p><p>All eligible users who submitted a BSC wallet during the whitelist registration can claim the airdrop and receive the upgraded POLX token in your wallet. We felt it would be unfair to expect the winners to participate in a token upgrade within days of receiving the airdrop and hence, we had to make the difficult choice to withhold the release of the airdrop to eligible users until the upgrade was live.</p><h4><strong>To claim your airdrop rewards:</strong></h4><ul><li>Login to the web portal: <a href="https://portal.polylastic.io/">https://portal.polylastic.io/</a> and navigate to the “Airdrop” tab.</li><li>Connect with the Metamask account corresponding to the BSC address that was supplied during the whitelist registration prior to the IDO.</li><li>Click on “Claim” and complete the transaction on Metamask.</li><li>Once the transaction is confirmed, you will receive 1550 POLX (new version) into your whitelisted address.</li></ul><p>We would like to thank our community for the patience and support. The introduction of network taxation via the token upgrade heralds a new era for Polylastic. We welcome you onboard this exciting journey.</p><h3><strong>-Polylastic</strong></h3><p><a href="http://polylastic.io/"><strong>Website</strong></a><strong> | </strong><a href="https://twitter.com/polylastic"><strong>Twitter</strong></a><strong> | </strong><a href="https://t.me/polylastic"><strong>Telegram</strong></a></p><img src="https://medium.com/_/stat?event=post.clientViewed&referrerSource=full_rss&postId=c6dd3f2b725c" width="1" height="1" alt=""> ]]>
</content:encoded>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[ Satoshi Club: A Polylastic Ecosystem Champion ]]>
</title>
<link>https://polylastic.medium.com/satoshi-club-a-polylastic-ecosystem-champion-6fa37f54454f?source=rss-5cf14b881f98------2</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://medium.com/p/6fa37f54454f</guid>
<category>
<![CDATA[ polylastic ]]>
</category>
<category>
<![CDATA[ ama ]]>
</category>
<category>
<![CDATA[ satoshiclub ]]>
</category>
<category>
<![CDATA[ polx ]]>
</category>
<category>
<![CDATA[ ecosystem-champion ]]>
</category>
<dc:creator>
<![CDATA[ Polylastic ]]>
</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2021 16:41:52 GMT</pubDate>
<atom:updated>2021-06-03T16:41:52.414Z</atom:updated>
<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[ <figure><img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*yD8QmKIdggv4dvTqeTX4Tg.jpeg" /></figure><p>We have been championing the growth of this emerging market sector for a while now and are glad to partner with more communities that are working towards creating knowledge and exposure to this nascent asset class. It is hard for new projects in this space as well as in-market users to be informed at all times of the changes in the industry. At Polylastic we are here to bring more exposure to the projects we will be nurturing and aggregate these assets before funnelling and distilling them into our intuitive index.</p><p>We understand that although identifying opportunity is important, there is a need to go further by nurturing and fostering growth. Because of this realization, we have made it our mission to compile resources and partners in order to streamline this path. This is the idea behind our Ecosystem Champions program. The champions we partner with have the capacity to provide exposure, guidance, community support and in the long run, generate an informed user base for the projects. As a platform, we are moving forward into nurturing the next generation of digital finance projects, which are evolving each day.</p><p><strong>Polylastic partners with Satoshi Club</strong></p><p>We are therefore thrilled to announce our new partnership with Satoshi Club, making it the newest project to join as an Ecosystem Champion. We are looking forward to all the impact that the partnership will deliver.</p><p>Satoshi Club is an educational group about crypto and blockchain technologies. It represents a place where crypto projects can grow. Satoshi Club has around 100,000 members cumulatively on its social media platforms, and is growing every day. Through its social media channels, Satoshi Club conducts educational sessions about crypto projects, which attracts many viewers, feedback and information sharing which is important for any project. Through its popular AMA sessions, Satoshi Club can interact with the community, answer questions about the project of the day and educate the community.</p><p><strong>How the partnership will impact the community and Ecosystem Champions</strong></p><p>The mission behind Ecosystem Champions is the incremental new users to grow the projects’ communities. Through these collaborations, the projects we nurture will have well programmed launches, pre- and post-marketing campaigns and initiatives to best prepare them for the crypto market.</p><p>Satoshi Club has planned and executed more than 700 AMA projects so far with notable projects in the market such as Cardano, Litecoin, Orion Protocol, KuCoin, Monero and many others. Its impact will go a long way in helping our projects to achieve the success they need. It will also allow the community to learn more about all projects, opening the projects up to more users and potential investors.</p><h3>- Polylastic</h3><p><a href="http://polylastic.io/">Website</a> | <a href="https://twitter.com/polylastic">Twitter</a> | <a href="https://t.me/polylastic">Telegram</a></p><h3>About CryptoDiffer</h3><p><a href="https://esatoshi.club/">Website</a> | <a href="https://twitter.com/esatoshiclub">Twitter</a> | <a href="https://t.me/satoshi_club_channel">Telegram</a></p><h3>About Ecosystem Champions:</h3><p>In addition to making it easy for everyone to invest into our buckets of indices, we are working on creating a trustworthy ecosystem where we can nurture projects and launch them. We do not want to be a standalone launchpad/ incubator. But to do what we want to do, we have to take the responsibility of passing the knowledge we have gained during our own token launch to help high quality projects that are yet to be launched in this space. So, we have forged strong partnerships with popular stakeholders who we call, Ecosystem Champions in the digital asset space.</p><img src="https://medium.com/_/stat?event=post.clientViewed&referrerSource=full_rss&postId=6fa37f54454f" width="1" height="1" alt=""> ]]>
</content:encoded>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[ The Burn of a Lifetime! ]]>
</title>
<link>https://polylastic.medium.com/the-burn-of-a-lifetime-a54db85c02e2?source=rss-5cf14b881f98------2</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://medium.com/p/a54db85c02e2</guid>
<category>
<![CDATA[ polylastic-token-burn ]]>
</category>
<category>
<![CDATA[ polylastic ]]>
</category>
<category>
<![CDATA[ polx-burn ]]>
</category>
<category>
<![CDATA[ polylastic-network-tax ]]>
</category>
<category>
<![CDATA[ polx ]]>
</category>
<dc:creator>
<![CDATA[ Polylastic ]]>
</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 18:35:33 GMT</pubDate>
<atom:updated>2021-06-03T10:35:23.909Z</atom:updated>
<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[ <figure><img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*EavtEIEF6fF2i8he7Ntpwg.jpeg" /></figure><p>As our advocates and POLX army personnel well know, there is a token upgrade slated to take place on June 4th. This of course involves the implementation of the taxation structure and our never ending quest to build the unbreakable digital asset.</p><p>While we have asked our earliest supporters to be patient as we iterate forward, Polylastic felt it was incumbent upon us to reward those users. As is often the case in crypto, we have experienced great speculation and commensurate volatility in a short time. The space grows like no other, contracting and expanding in ways that are both exhilarating and uncomfortable. Nonetheless, we adhere to our vision and move forward as market cycles complete as if they were cooked in a microwaves.</p><h4>Crossing the Bridge</h4><p>In order to effectuate the upgrade, the POLX tokens must essentially migrate to a new version and this represented an opportunity to reward our initial visionaries. Hence, we decided to not impose any network tax whilst upgrading the current circulating tokens.</p><p>Network taxation, once live, represents an ongoing fee and burn structure to support the POLX token and drive scarcity. Prior to this, interested parties have had a chance to build their position and glimpse what is forthcoming.</p><p>While these numbers are not exact, they do represent an accurate approximation of what we have proposed:</p><ul><li>Circulating Supply: ~10B</li><li>Vesting &amp; Locked: ~90B</li></ul><p>The circulating supply will be untouched and remain 10B, however, the currently sidelined 90B will be subjected to the first network tax and it is a big one:</p><ul><li>~90B x 2% =1.8B POLX</li><li>20% or approximately <strong>360M POLX will be burnt</strong></li><li>approximately <strong>1.44B POLX</strong> will be used to incentivize and reward users</li></ul><p>While the burn will happen upon migration, please understand that the additional 1.44B are largely vesting tokens and will only be accessible upon release. As vesting completes, they will be placed into a treasury and earmarked for incentives for users.</p><p>This represents a truly massive step forward and shows Polylastic’s willingness to practice what they preach. An aggressive network tax is the proverbial rose with thorns—its sting is felt upon leaving while its beauty lies in its benefit to long-term supporters.</p><h3>-Polylastic</h3><p><a href="http://polylastic.io/">Website</a> | <a href="https://twitter.com/polylastic">Twitter</a> | <a href="https://t.me/polylastic">Telegram</a></p><img src="https://medium.com/_/stat?event=post.clientViewed&referrerSource=full_rss&postId=a54db85c02e2" width="1" height="1" alt=""> ]]>
</content:encoded>
</item>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[ Introducing Polylastic Boost ]]>
</title>
<link>https://polylastic.medium.com/introducing-polylastic-boost-2655083201cc?source=rss-5cf14b881f98------2</link>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://medium.com/p/2655083201cc</guid>
<category>
<![CDATA[ polylastic ]]>
</category>
<category>
<![CDATA[ index-funds ]]>
</category>
<category>
<![CDATA[ crypto-marketing ]]>
</category>
<category>
<![CDATA[ polylastic-boost ]]>
</category>
<category>
<![CDATA[ airdrop ]]>
</category>
<dc:creator>
<![CDATA[ Polylastic ]]>
</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 12:05:37 GMT</pubDate>
<atom:updated>2021-06-01T12:05:37.590Z</atom:updated>
<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[ <figure><img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*jgOqo0vOX0gJN1Gf7apoQg.jpeg" /></figure><p>The Polylastic community is growing stronger day after day. Right from day 1, our community has backed us and has been the main driving factor behind our successful launch. This support has only grown stronger since launch. The active and engaged community is going to be the fuel that will power our community weighted indices. In order to nurture and grow our community, we are introducing <strong>Polylastic Boost</strong>, a digital co-marketing platform that will reward our users for spreading the word about our partnerships and collaborations.</p><p><strong>What would a typical Boost campaign comprise of?</strong></p><ul><li>Listing on the Polylastic Aggregator: The Polylastic aggregator is the first step for projects to get featured in our community weighted indices. Only those projects that are listed on our aggregator will be considered for the community voting rounds.</li><li>Joint announcements that will be covered by popular crypto channels and communities.</li><li>Co-marketing campaigns that will reward users for promoting the partnerships and the collaborations.</li><li>Custom campaigns eg: Joint AMAs, airdrops, etc to spread awareness about the partnered projects and Polylastic.</li></ul><p><strong>Interested to participate in the Polylastic Boost program?</strong></p><p>We have already built up a strong pipeline of projects that will be partnering with us and participating in the Polylastic Boost program. If you are part of or represent a project that can benefit from this program, we would love to hear from you. Please fill up <a href="https://forms.gle/SW19wrPd1ztkzYvA6"><strong><em>this application form</em></strong></a> and we will be in touch.</p><p><strong>Benefits to our community</strong></p><p>We are confident that the Polylastic Boost platform will reward our community in multiple ways, including, but not limited to:</p><ul><li>Rewards in POLX tokens and the project’s tokens in return for the community’s efforts.</li><li>Exposure to interesting projects that are likely to be of good quality.</li><li>Ability to get your favourite projects listed on the Polylastic aggregator and Indices (subject to community voting).</li><li>Part of the revenues generated from the Boost campaigns will be used to buy back and burn POLX tokens.</li><li>Improved visibility for Polylastic that could help acquire new users and communities.</li></ul><h3>- Polylastic</h3><p><a href="http://polylastic.io/">Website</a> | <a href="https://twitter.com/polylastic">Twitter</a> | <a href="https://t.me/polylastic">Telegram</a></p><img src="https://medium.com/_/stat?event=post.clientViewed&referrerSource=full_rss&postId=2655083201cc" width="1" height="1" alt=""> ]]>
</content:encoded>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>